<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Raimon Grau</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Raimon Grau</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 17:45:12 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic libs with Nix&#43;Racket</title>
      <link>/post/2020-07-05-racket-and-nix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 17:45:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020-07-05-racket-and-nix/</guid>
      <description>When installing a package with nix-shell, you get a temporary profile that contains everything that was on your parent profile (where you ran nix-shell) plus the installed packages from that nix-shell command.
nixpkgs repo is big and generally ok, but there are hurdles here and there, that you must be able to jump if you want to walk least-walked-paths.
Let&amp;rsquo;s see what happens (from my dimm understanding still) when you install a dynamic library that is not directly linked from your installed packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fridge-O-Mattic</title>
      <link>/post/2020-05-30-fridge-o-mattic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 23:43:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020-05-30-fridge-o-mattic/</guid>
      <description>Parts:  arduino uno Ultrasonic Distance Sensor (HC-SR04) 2 leds buzzer? lcd screen a fridge MAGNETS! (of course, the secret sauce)  
Story Small hacky project where by installing an arduino with some very basic sensors, you can detect when the fridge&amp;rsquo;s door is left open.
Maybe you can relate, maybe not, but the fridge at my new place has some issues when closing the door, and sometimes it doesn&amp;rsquo;t close properly (you have to make sure every time it&amp;rsquo;s been properly closed, and not 99% closed)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Constraint Programming with CL Screamer</title>
      <link>/post/constraint-programming-with-screamer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 02:42:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/constraint-programming-with-screamer/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to get into Lisp again and last week it came to my hands a problem that looked like a perfect case for giving CL another try.
The problem is about a very special sudoku with only 4 initial values. The sudoku has, of course special rules:
 The square in the middle is a magic square (all rows,columns, and digonals add up the same). Both diagonals of the board can&amp;rsquo;t have repeated numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This site</title>
      <link>/post/learning-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 22:04:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/learning-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Setting up this website</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 10:39:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello, world!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>